Priyanka Khadilkar

Full-Stack Developer

priyanka140592@gmail.com

6476870653

Toronto, Canada ♀

linkedin.com/in/priyankakhadilkar in

github.com/Priyanka-Khadilkar

Seeking for a Full-Stack developer position in a fast growing organization to utilize my 6 years of expertise in software development projects using front end and back end technologies. As well as deployment and support using software development methodologies, coming with well honed skills in software development in addition to excellent communication skills.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages	C#, PHP, Core Java, Javascript	Web Technologies	ASP.NET MVC, WCF, Web API, Web Services(SOAP, REST)
Front-end Technologies	HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, Boostrap, Durandal JS, Knockout JS, Typescript, JSON, XML, AJAX, NodeJS, AngularJS, ExpressJS	Database	MS SQL, MySQL, MongoDB
Version Control Tool	GIT, TFS, VSTS, Tortoise SVN	IDE(S)/Tools	Visual Studio, PHPStrom, Adobe Photoshop, PHPMyAdmin, GitHub, WordPress, Visual Studio Code
Software Development Methodologies	Agile, Waterfall	MS-Office	Word, Outlook, Excel and PowerPoint

WORK EXPERIENCE

Engineer || S&P Global

07/2017 – 07/2019 Ahmedabad, India

Achievements/Tasks

- Involved in Requirement gathering, design, development, testing, wire frame creation and implementation of the web
 application and used software development life cycle.
- Built rich front-end applications, user interactive (UI) web pages using HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Knockout JS, DurandalJS,
 Typescript, JavaScript and jQuery that meets accessibility and web browser standards for website.
- Followed complete Agile methodology for product development. Effectively communicated within different teams in the
 organization to get the product developed as per the details specified in the feature/requirement without any flaws following
 complete SDLC life cycle.
- Debugged various defects during project support phase after the feature development.
- Provided support during production release and debugged defects in production environment to ensure customer satisfaction and products is working without any flaws.
- Rewarded on multiple occasion with "Bronze Award" by Product Owner, Scrum Master and Project Managers.

Engineer

Einfochips Pvt Ltd

05/2014 – 07/2017 Ahmedabad, India

Achievements/Tasks

- Involved in Requirement gathering, design, development, testing and implementation of the web application using C#,
 ASP.NET MVC, HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery and used software development life cycle.
- Communicated with clients for design, requirements and queries. Wrote, updated and maintained specification, end user documentation and operational procedures.
- Performed code review as and when required. Provided technical assistance to other software developers/Co-workers.
- Followed Agile SCRUM Developmental approach to deliver product releases by SPRINT processes in an iterative and incremental approach (SCRUM).
- Built Proof of concept for clients using MEAN(Mongo DB, ExpressJS, AngularJS, NodeJS) Stack and Sharepoint 2013.
- Rewarded on multiple occasions with "Pat on the Back" award and high level client appreciation.

Page 1 of 2

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jr. .net Developer

Sigma Solve

07/2013 – 05/2014 Ahmedabad, India

- Achievements/Tasks
- Developed software applications using C#, ASP.NET, XML, HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, MSSQL, MVC, WCF, KnockoutJS and Boostrap.
- Involved in write application level code to interact with APIs, Web Services using AJAX, JSON and XML.Responsible for creating RESTFUL Web Services to serve data to the front-end application in JSON format.
- Supported and maintained business applications. Investigated and Resolved bugs.
- Wrote, updated and maintained specification, end user documentation and operational procedures.
- Evaluated new technologies in the light of emerging trends and technologies.
- Communicated with clients for design, requirements, and queries effectively.

SOFT SKILLS

Teamwork

Flexibility

Problem Solving

Strategic

Learner

Focus

Communication

CERTIFICATES

Microsoft - Developing ASP.NET MVC Web Applications (07/2016)

LinkedIn - Node.js for C# Developer (04/2019)

M101N: MongoDB for .NET Developers (05/2015)

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering

Gujarat Technological University

2009 – 2013

Ahmedabad , India 7.60GPA

Web development Post-Graduate

Humber College

2019 – Present Toronto, Canada

LANGUAGES

English
Full Professional Proficiency

.

Hindi Native or Bilingual Proficiency Gujarati

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Marathi

Full Professional Proficiency

REFERENCES

References available on request.